after what started This is how
после чего началось Вот это как-то
Palestinian children die because of What did they
умирать палестинские дети из-за Чего
start dying after after no
начали умирать после после того как нет
Palestinian Children are dying a long time ago this is
палестинские Дети умирают ещ давно вот
no agreement children were dying a long time
это вот нетт договорн дети умирали ещ
ago but it was a long time ago yes But
давно давно а вот давно было да А вот
now this is what happened that Nago when
сейчас вот что случилось что Наго когда
Hama came because they were starting to
хама нал потому что начина
seize Hamas attacked Hamas shot at
захватывать Хамас напал Хамас стрелял на
you Hamas attacked Israel no he didn't attack Israel
вас Хамас напал на Израиль да не напал
He wanted to get his
на Израиль Он хотел вернуть свою
country back Hello hello I'm from the city of
страну Здравствуй здравствуй Я из города
Khmelnitsky where are you from I'm from the city of
Хмельницке Ты откуда Я из города
Moscow and one two three times I
Москвы и раз два три
start what I thought you'll show PTO now
начинаю что я думал ты сейчас ПТО
you smile like that 2T show
покажешь ты так улыбайся 2Т показать ты
what I'm I'm
чего
tense I think now
я Я напряг думаю сейчас
some kind of you who is Armenian No not Armenian And
какой-то ты кто армянин Нет не армянин А
who am I an Arab Arab And where exactly are you from Well from
кто Я араб араб А откуда именно Ну из
Syria from Syria I understood And how long have you been living
Сирии из Сирии понял А как давно живёшь
in Russia Well from
в России Ну из
2020 no in 2012 I
2020 нет в 2012 году
understood And what do you communicate about Yes no I don't know
понял А чем общаешься о Да не не знаю
let him know I'm sitting there with anyone like a
пусть знает сижу там с кем попало как
butt  Listen, here's the question I looked at,
попа Слушай а вот вопрос я так смотрел в
mainly men come to Russia from Syria,
основном из Сирии в Россию приезжают
but women don't. Why is that? Why should
мужчины а женщины не приезжают Почему
women come only to go
так зачем женщинам приезжать только идти
to their families? Well, it turns out that you
к семьям своим Ну а так вы получается вы
men come and there are Russian
мужчины приезжают и там российских
women there. No, and what kind of girls do you
женщин Да нет а с с какими девушками вы
meet there in Russia? We
там встречаетесь в России ни с кем мы
take our women to Russia, and
свои женщины забираем в России а
from Syria. Yes, we get married. I understand. Yes, what is
из из Сирии Да женимся понял Да как Как
your wife's name? Why do you know my wife?
зовут твою жену Зачем тебя знат мою жену
It's personal. Well, does she have an Arabic name or
это лично Ну там у неё арабское имя или
Russian? No, it's Arabic. Well, for
русское Да нет арабское арабское Ну
example, I don't know Arabic names and what is
например я не знаю арабские имена и как
your name? There are a lot of them. My name is gays
тебя зовут там оче много Меня зовут гайс
gays. Yes, it's like H GU. No, it's gays.
гайс Да это как H GU Да нет это гайс
My name is gays. What does that mean
Меня зовут гайс А что это означает
in Arabic?
по-арабски
Rain. A strong hurricane. Rain. I
дождь Сильный ураган дождь
understand.
понял
Well, what's there? What flag do you have? I'm here and
Ну что там А что у тебя флаг это тут я а
this is just behind. Like, how can I
это это просто сзади Такой типа как тебе
tell you now? Now, this is my head. I'll
сказать сейчас сейчас сому это ВС голову
tell you. Well, it's
скажу Ну это
like, well, you understand. No, you have a
типа ну ты понял Нет яже ну у тебя там
green curtain there, like they say. No, this is
такая Зелёная шторка как они говорят вот
not a chroma key. This is a real flag.
не это не хромакея это реальный флаг а
This is a real flag.  you have a hall
это реальный флаг тебе зал
shoving a big flag at all costs we just have
сует на всю сину у нас просто у
Ukrainians like we have a tradition like this
украинцев типа у нас вот Традиция такая
when a child is born they sew him a
когда рождается ребёнок так ему шьют
big flag this flag when I was
большой флаг вот этот флаг когда я
born my parents sewed me one too and this this this
родился Мне тоже пошили родители и вот
g this in Ukraine We don't have that
это вот это г этог в Украине У нас нет
I was in Ukraine no it's just not
такого я был в Украины нет так просто не
everyone adheres to the tradition now
все в традиции придерживаются сейчас
many are already kind of moving away from the tradition just
многие уже как бы отходят от традиции
like you not everyone already
так же как у вас не все уже Ислам
contains Islam And so on Yes we have a
содержат И так дальше Да у нас вот
child born yes
родился ребёнок да
reb wait now a child is born they
реб подожди сейчас ребнок родился ему
sew him a big flag it's twisted live you
шьют большой флаг он скрученный жит тебе
by the way many more can you don't
кстати ещё многие тебе могут не
tell because it's a family
рассказывай потому что это семейная
heirloom Yes if you're not Ukrainian they don't
Реликвия Да если ты не украинец тебе не
tell you because well they don't trust you they don't
говорят потому что ну не доверяют они не
say where this family flag is you
говорят где этот флаг лежит семейный
understand Wait wait that is you
понимаешь Подожди подожди а то есть ты
trust me Dish you say this so no
мне доверяешь Диш это говоришь так нет
you won't take it from me you're somewhere far away like
ты же не заберёшь у меня ты далеко
that I mean why then should they why shouldn't they milk me I'll take them
где-то так В смысле А зачем тогда они
or something Now wait about this you
что ли Сейчас подожди про это ты
say you have a lot of Muslims who don't
говоришь у вас очень много мусульман не
keep this  we don't
держат это у нас традиция никто не
have any tradition What does tradition and
держит Причём тут традиция и
religion have to do with it religion is a kind of
религия религия - это разновидность
tradition Well this is a kind Here you
традиции Ну это разновидность Вот вы
Look what you are Muslims
Смотри ты какой Вы мусульмане
Alawites What kind of Alawites Well Sunnis Shiites
алавиты Какие алавиты Ну сунниты шииты
Alawites who are you no Alawites There are Sunnis
алавиты кто Вы нету алавиты Есть сунниты
Shiites only no Alawites there is this one
шиит только нет алавиты есть вот этот у
you have this one how is he Syrian Dictator what is
вас этот как он сирийский Диктатор как
his name Ashar Ashad he catches
его Ашар ашад он ловит
he doesn't tin this is Jesters no Now I'll
он не олови это Шутов нет Сейчас я тебе
look at you tin I'll explain to you wait no
посмотрю олови я тебе объясню постой не
need to look for Jesters there Look Jesters Jester there are
надо там искать Шутов смотри Шутов Шут
several types here Alawites there are these
разделяются несколько видов вот алавиты
Alawites yes this is Shui these are not
есть вот это алавиты да это Шуи это не
Shiites these are Alawites this is a kind of
шииты это алавиты это это разновидность
Jesters my good man I know better Shiites these are
Шутов мой хороший Я лучше знаю шииты это
Shiites in Iran yes And in Syria these are
вот в Иране шииты да А в Сирии это
Alawites they are also Shui but not What do you
алавиты они тоже Шуи но не Ты что что ты
know Damn are you a
разбираешься Блин ты что мусульманин
true Muslim No I mean not a true Muslim
истинный Нет в смысле не истинный
you are not a true Muslim
мусульманин ты не истинный
Muslim why why why How do
мусульманин почему а почему а почему Как
you How do you prove how do you
ты Как ты докажешь как Ты
testify true
засвидетельствуете истинный
Muslim Islam is in the heart
мусульманин мусульманство - это в сердце
just like you don't what does it mean in the heart
так же как ве не не что значит в сердце
Hello How do you know the Koran Do you have it Yes of
Алло А как тебя так Коран У тебя есть Да
course Show me oh now I'll show you
конечно Покажи ой сейчас тебе покажу
now
сейчас тебе
I'll show you now I'll
покажу сейчас я тебе
show you So what year was the Koran released Oh I do
покажу Так какого года выпуска Коран О я
n't know who who is the publisher who is the publisher
не знаю кто кто издатель кто издатель
Look who is the
Посмотри кто
publisher this is the court
издатель это судская
Ara
Ара
Ari
Ари
publisher court
издатель суд
aravi I know got it yeah But look not like that
арави знаю понял да А вот смотри не так
No not isti like or not one Why
Нет не исти типа или нет од одну Почему
what surah do you know by heart I know so
какую суру ты на память знаешь я Поче
many surahs by heart Well well what do you
много Сули на память знаю А ну ну что ты
want which one Tell me
хочешь какую Скажи мне
about the story when Muhammad entered
про историю когда Мухамед входил в
Medina when Enter Medina it's called
медину когда Входи медину это называется
razr Come on tell me this
разр Давай расскажи эту
su I'm telling you and how
су тебе рассказываю а как те на русском
should you tell it in Russian it's difficult Yeah it
должно это рассказать это сложно Ага
means you don't know no no one thing I don't know
значит не знаешь нет нет одно не знаю
one thing when to translate it's all difficult no don't
одно когда переводить это всё тяжело не
give come on here steam they collected everything
не давай давай вотт пар это собрали все
before that when Muhammad came out his
до этого когда Мухаммед вышел его же
parents him from his  family Well, like from
родители его из его семьёй Ну типа из
his population there are friends like his father They
его населения там друзья типа отца Они
wanted to kill him only his uncle I
хотели его убить только его дядя это я
will tell you from the very beginning Okay no
тебе с самого начала расскажу Хорошо
no You sura specifically about entering
нене Ты суру конкретно о вхождение в
Medina you you should as a Muslim
медину ты ты должен по как мусульманин
Yes you should remember What sura is about entering
Да должен помнить Какая Сура входе
Medina such and no What are you Listen to the Quran
Медине такое и нет Ты что Слушай Коран
when the prophet Quran When God gave
когда пророку Корану Когда Бог дал
meant How do you say the format when the
означал Как там теб формат сказать когда
prophet Muhammad wrote the Quran he drank
пророк Мухаммад написал Коран он пил
time until before death You see he
время пока перед смертью Понимаешь он не
could not attribute what he did
мог приписать то что он сделал потому
because the Quran comes to him from an angel
что Коран приходит у него с ангела
that God sends correctly do you
который Бог присылает правильно ты
remember this sura when you remember
помнишь вот эту суру когда ты помнишь
when the
когда
angel This is how he is in your opinion Jabrail Yes
ангел Это как он по вашему джебраил Да
when the angel Jabrail in Arabic the angel
когда ангел джебраил по-арабски ангел
Jabrail appeared to
джебраил явился
Muhammad at the moment of entering Medina
мухаммаду в момент вхождения в медину
so he said these evil golden gates of
так он сказал вот эти зло золотые врата
Medina here I am just in Russian I am
медины вот я я просто по-русски я
in Arabic well I can not repeat This is
по-арабски ну не могу повторить Это
because Yes that's how it sounded that
потому что Да вот э там как звучало что
Muhammad appeared before the golden
и предстал Мухаммад перед золотыми
gates of Medina and appeared to him  Archangel
вратами медины и явился ему Архангел
Gabriel said Muhammad go you will
джебраил и сказал Мухаммад иди ты
enter now into these golden gates and
войдёшь сейчас в эти врата золотые и
become a prophet for and you will carry the
станешь пророком ибо и будешь нести
message throughout the world and after entering the
весть по всему миру и после вхождения в
Medina gates you will become the leader of all
мединские врата ты станешь лидером всех
Muslims and now wait wait and
мусульман и сейчас подожди подожди и
now Muhammad you have a choice either
сейчас Мухаммад У тебя есть выбор либо
you
ты
turn around and lead a worldly
разворачивается и будешь вести мирский
about the worldly way of life or you will enter
об Мирской образ жизни либо ты войдёшь в
these gates and there will be no turning back you
эти врата и пути назад не будет ты
will become a prophet forever and ever and until the
станешь пророком на веки веков и до
second Coming until the end of the
второго Пришествия пока не будет конец
world until the sun rises at sunset
Света пока не взойдёт на закате солнца
you will be a flag for all Muslims
ты будешь флагом для всех мусульман
remember this if you find it for me
помнишь это если ты мне найдёшь это
now you will find what I do not have a Quran
сейчас найдёшь какую У меня нету Корана
with me next to the Internet I think through the
с собой рядо в Интернете я думаю чере в
Internet What are you What kind of Muslim on the
интернете Ты что Что за мусульманин в
Internet will read the Quran The Quran is
интернете Коран будет читать Коран
only printed there is a Surah and the entry Well
только печатный есть Сура а вхождение Ну
then you then you tell me how the Surah about
тогда ты тогда ты расскажи как Сура о
entering Medina Come on it was very
вхождении в медину Давай это очень было
ka there is no Surah about entering Medina
ка Сура вхождения в Медине нету
su is when Muhammad entered Medina
су есть когда Мухаммад входил в медину
this Sign was Now wait wait
это Знамение было Сейчас подожди подожди
I'll clarify but I'm sure there is none Ask
я уточ но я уверен что нету Спроси у
your mule Who is who at the mule ask your mule
своего Кто кто у мулы спроси своего
what kind of
какой
priest is What is your
мулы священник Как у тебя называется
Sheikh called Now
Шейх Сейчас
wait I'm interested
подожди мне интересно
he then also said a prophecy about the temple
он тогда ещё сказал пророчество про храм
alaq about the mosque aks that it will be
аляк про мечеть акс что она будет
captured by the
захвачена
infidels you are just one of those Muslims
неверными ты просто из тех мусульман
who
которые
demonstratively once a year on some ran bayram
показательно раз в год на ран байрам
come to bow down do namaz
какой-то придут поклонятся сделают намаз
and that's it You perform namaz five times a
и всё Ты намаз исполняешь пять раз в
day Show me your
день Покажи коврик для
prayer mat I don't have a mat I am in Norway with
намаза у меня нет коврика Я в Норвегии
you how do you perform namaz
нахожусь у тебя как Ты совершаешь намаз
without a prayer mat So what do you know about
без коврика для намаза Так ты что знаешь
Islam mushina so that
мусульманство мушина чтобы
you are simply Alawi what kind of Alawi Alawi and Shi
просто ты алави какой алави алави и ши
that's all what kind of Sunni are you I am a Sunni not a Sunni you are
это всё какой ты суннит я суннит не суни
some kind of Shiite or Awit
ты Ты какой-то либо шиит либо авит
really a sect or in general you are
реально секта или вообще ты вообще Суфи
some kind of Sufi probably
какой-то наверное
yes they sent all these sectarians when
да послали этих сектантов всяких когда
when during Muhammad  there were no
когда во время Мухамеда было не было
Shiites all kinds of Sui Yes everything was there was the Ummah of the
шиитов всяких суи Да всё было было Умма
mind was united and monolithic and
ума была едина и монолитно и
indivisible well indivisible find me in the
нераздельная ну нераздельная найди мне в
Koran the division into Shiites and Sunnis
Коране разделение на шиитов и суннитов
find it like that What do I need to find here I am a Sunni I
найди так Причём тут найти я суннит мне
dont need You know what disconnects You
не надо Ты знаешь чем отключается Ты
know what disconnects a Suite from a Sunni
знаешь чем отключается суит от суннитов
Look again find find me in the
Вот смотри ещё раз найди найди мне в
Koran where it says on the division of a Suite from a Sunni Suite from a Sunni
Коране где написано на разделение суита
while you are
вишита суита вишита пока ты
Muslim Islam is one and if you
мусульманство Ислам един и если ты
start saying I am a Sunni I am a Shiite you are already
начинаешь говорить я суни я шиит ты уже
dividing Islam where do you know the
делишь мусульманство де де Ты знаешь
difference You are dividing you are saying I am a Sunni You
разни Ты делишь ты говоришь я суннит Ты
must speak You must speak I am a
должен говорить Ты должен говорить Я
Muslim I am a Muslim and thats it Why Why are
мусульманин Я мусульманин и всё Зачем
you dividing Why are you dividing
Зачем Ты делишь Зачем Ты делишь
look Muhammad was a Sunni [ __ ] or a
смотри Мухаммад был суним шитом или
Muslim
мусульманином
wait please
стой пожалуйста
lets do it this way Prophet Muhammad was a Sunni
давай так Пророк Мухаммед был суним
[ __ ] Or did he say that he was a Muslim
шитом Или он говорил что он мусульманин
Can I tell you he was a flax no you cant
Можно я расскажу он был льн нет нельзя
he was a Suite  Or Shini he was a
он был суит Или шини он был мульма
Muslim, everything he did not divide Sunni and
мусульманин всё он не разделял суннит
Shiite as you understand because it is
шиит так как ты понимаешь потому что это
from Iblis It is from Iblis the shaitans the shaitan
от Иблиса Это от Иблиса шайтаны шайтан
look the shaitan what did he do he took the ummah
смотри шайтан что сделал он взял умму
divided there are Shiites there are
разделил там шииты там
Sunnis stink
сунниты вони
you are zero in the Koran but I will tell you this is
ты в Коране ноль но я тебе скажу это
because
из-за того что
you do not go to the mosque
ты не ходишь в мечеть ты не посещаешь
you do not attend namaz you do not follow the precepts of the Koran for
намаз ты не следуешь заветам Корана для
you it is an empty sound you took it read and that's it You do not
тебя это пустой звук взял почитал да и
live by these traps Why did
всё Ты не живёшь По этим западни Почему
you betray your country you ran away from
ты ты свою страну предал ты убежал из
your
своей
country the country where everything is imbued with the spirit of the
страны страны где всё пропитано духом
ancestors the spirit of Muslims the prophet and went
предков духом мусульман пророко и поехал
to Norway to Vikin to the northern Vikings Yes
в Норвегию на Викин к викингам северным
Christianity Yes Norway Why do you go to
Да христианство Да Норвегия Что ходишь
church in Norway already Yes you pray there to
уже в церковь в Норвегию Да молишься там
Jesus Yes that's how you betrayed Yes
Иисусу Да вот так вот предал Да потому
because Iblis or for money Yes because they
что иблис или за деньги Да потому что
pay more in Norway is it
платят в Норвегии больше
true You betrayed You betrayed Syria because
правда Ты предал Ты предал Сирию потому
legs
что ноги
really You betrayed your country  you
реально Ты предал свою страну ты
say where you were born
говори где роди
really really the place where you were born or
реально реально место где ты родился что
something Yes you are a Jew I am a Jew you are a Jew I am a
ли Да ты еврей я еврей ты еврей я еврей
Jew Come on Yes I am a
Да я еврей который принял мусульманство
Jew who converted to Islam you are a Jew who converted to Islam and
ты еврей который принял мусульманство и
you don't know the difference between Shitov and because
ты не знаешь разниц Между Шитов и потому
I am a true
что я истинный
Muslim true Muslims will not go away
мусульманин истинные мусульмане не дется
ours I will say Look because uh Prophet
наши скажу Смотри потому что э Пророк
Muhammad was also a Jew and then converted to
Мухаммед тоже был евреем а потом принял
Islam Prophet Muhammad was a Jew
мусульманство пророк Мухаммад был евреем
Yes and then converted to Islam Yes where is this where do
Да а потом принял мусульманство Да это
you remember Jerusalem
где это где ты помнишь Иерусалимский
campaign his who is who Surah about the Jerusalem
поход его кто кто Сура о иерусалимском
campaign of Muhammad when he came to the temple
походе Мухаммада когда он пришёл в храм
Alex do you remember in the mosque Alex
Алекс помнишь в мечеть Алекс
Well well in Jerusalem temple Alex Don't you
Ну ну в Иерусалиме храм Алекс Ты что не
know do
зна
n't you know temple
не знаешь храм
and the main temple the main mosque in
а гла главный храм главная мечеть в
Jerusalem I
Иерусалиме я
have shaitan ate your soul just ate
тели шайтан твою душу съел просто съел
you up
ты
with a triangle and a look Are you really
до с треугольником и Взглядом Ты реально
there this is generally Quiet this is generally Quiet
там это это вообще Тихо это вообще Тихо
I am
я
those thanks to this
те благодаря это
American Look I will tell you now I am
американс Смотри я сейчас тебе скажу я
generally I am from Israel I am from Israel So you are
вообще я из Израиля Я из Израиля Так ты
from Israel yes Oh by the way I will give you a song
из Израиля да О кстати я тебе песню
look at ours Here is a song song And you too
смотри на наша Вот песня песня И ты тоже
you should know it too
ты её тоже должен знать
everyone Here who does not divide into Shiites
каждый Вот кто не делит на шиитов
Sunnis Everyone should know the
суннитов Каждый должен знать э
song Prophet Muhammad also loves it
песня пророк Мухаммад тоже её любит
Nagila is not full
Нагила не
Uva va Uva
сыта Ува вя Ува
and by the way how do you feel about the fact that
а кстати как ты относишься к тому что
Hamas is shelling Israel that's how it should be Well
Хамас обстреливает Израиль так и надо Ну
you support Hamas terrorists for
ты поддерживаешь террористов Хамаса для
you they are
вас они
terrorists as for you they are terrorists
террористы как для вас они террористы
as is Russia which So wait so
как и Россия которы Так подожди так
look well Hamas look attacked Israel
смотри ну Хамас смотри напал на Израиль
Yes captured children killed hostages
Да захватил детей поубивал заложников
captured Go back Go back to
захватил Возвращайся Возвращайся к
World War II what Israel you
Второй мировой войне какой Израиль вас и
never existed wait
не
Well look Hamas look
было подожди Ну смотри Хамас смотри
Hamas there is Fatah I understand in
Хамас вот есть фатх я я понимаю в
Palestine the legitimate authority is
палестине законная власть - это
Fatah that's it don't wait look here I am
фатх во это не подожди вот смотри вот я
Yasser Yasser Arafat
Ясир Ясир Арафат организация
Palestine Liberation Organization here he is Yes here is
освобождения Палестины вот он Да вот
Palestine Yes there is here and Hamas They
Палестина Да есть вот а Хамас Они
captured Palestine Sya group
захватили палестину ся группировка
which in Palestine
которая в палестине
captured Palestine  Hamas Hamas
захватили палестину Хамас Хамас
occupied the Gaza Strip in Palestine who are they
оккупировал Сектор газа в палестине
shooting at They they are shooting
они в кого стреляют они Они они стреляют
Hamas shot Palestinians Fatah Yes They
Хамас расстрелял палестинцев фатх Да
drank Fatah and also attacked Israel
Выпили фатх и ещё и напали на Израиль
They killed Fatah Yes to fight Israel Yes why why
Они фатх убили Да на бой на Израиль Да
why in the Strip from the
почему почему почему в секторе из
Gaza Strip the real
Сектора Газа изгнано реальное
government of Palestine was expelled the government of
правительство Палестины правительство
Palestine Where in Ramallah is it
Палестины Где в ра мале
true that the president
правда тот президент
Abla the president sits just supports
абла президент сидит просто поддерживает
Israel Wait Stop the law stop is there a legitimate
Израиля Подожди Стоп закон стоп законный
president of Palestine yes you are some kind of
президент Палестины есть да ты какой-то
from Syria who is now in Norway Yes you
из Сирии который сейчас в Норвегии Да
start saying that he is somehow
начинаешь рассказывать что он какой-то
not like that yes he is not like that not even I
не такой да он не такой даже не я это
say this all the Arabs say this No well
говорю все арабы это говорят Не ну
wait why don't the Arabs in Palestine
подожди а почему арабы в палестине такое
say such things They
не говорят Они же его
elect him Who is elected by whom this is how who
избирают Кого кто избирает это как кто
elects Well who elected the president of
избирает Ну а кто избрал президента
Palestine here is Fatah or who is there
Палестины вот фатх или кто там
Israel how Israel elected the president of
Израиль как Израиль избрал президента
Palestine like that unfortunately like that like that that
Палестины вот так во вот к сожалению вот
is wait wait wait wait
так вот так то есть подожди подожди
Well look Wait
подожди подожди Ну смотри Подожди
wait Come on now  let's start over again
подожди Давай сейчас начинаем заново
Dava over again you are from Israel you are not I am not from
Дава заново ты из Израиль ты нет Я не из
Israel
Израиля Я из
I am from Jordan you are from Jordan I am in
Иордании ты из Иордании Я сейчас в
Israel now just for a week And so I am from Jordan
Израиле просто на неделю А так я из
Yes I am in Jordan Jordan yes
Иордании Да я Иордане Иордане да
so in
так в
general listen you sweat in Israel and you
общем слушай ты поты в Израиля и ты
think that
думаешь что
Israel attacked it Hamas Yes yes I
Израиль напали на неё Хамас Да да я
saw I saw how these Hamas Yes they
видел я видел как вот эти Хамас Да
showed the killed children Yes how they
убитых детей показывали Да как они
transported a woman from Germany Yes a tourist with
возили женщину из Германии Да туристку с
broken legs Yes they transported
поломанными ногами Да на машине возили
there by car mocking how They captured ordinary people at the
там глуми как Они захватили простых
festival this was Zelensky
фестивале это было вам Зеленский
told you this No no they showed it
рассказал это Нет нет это показывали
Arab channels showed it too you know
арабские каналы показывали тоже знаешь
what a pity a pity that Hitler did not get
что жалко жалко что Гитлер не добывал
you this and it is a pity seriously he said I will
вас это и жалко серьёзно он сказал я
leave you e nations so that you know what it
оставлю вам э нации чтобы узнала что
was a pity seriously a pity it is just simply that
было жалко серьёзно жалко просто просто
you such people act worse than
вы такие люди поступаете е хуже
Hitler in prey I understand that is you I understand
Гитлера пожива понял то есть ты я понял
that is you are a Syrian who now lives in
то есть ты сириец который сейчас живёт в
Norway You are in Norway yes yes yes yes you
Норвегии Ты же в Норвегии да да да да ты
turn out to say that e It is a pity that Hitler did
получается говори что э Жалко что Гитлер
not destroy all the Jews Yes because  that the
не уничтожил всех евреев Да потому что
Jews are now being destroyed by the Palestinian
евреев сейчас уничтожают палестинский
People In short, listen, how do you think,
Наро Короче слушай а как вот ты считаешь
if the Norwegian authorities Yes, uh, find out
вот если власти Норвегии Да ээ узнают
that you support Hitler and
что ты поддерживаешь Гитлера да и такое
say such things, will they deport you or not, no I have
говоришь они тебя депортируют или нет
citizenship,
нет У меня гражданство
but they will put you in jail No, you do
а посадят
nt know why Because
Нет знаешь почему Потому что у нас
unlike you, we have democracy, I can
отличие от Вас демократия есть я могу
say what I want to have, what I want, the main thing is
говорить что хочу иметь что хочу главное
you, you, you, can you, like, in short, Jews Yes, you want to say
ты ты ты ты можешь типа короче евреев Да
No, no Listen, I can
хочешь сказать Нет нет Слушай я могу
say what I want, but no one is being killed, there are
говорить что хочу но не убывает никого
two different things here For example, if you,
тут две разные вещи Вот например если ты
if some Ukrainian says I am
если кто какой-нибудь украинец скажет я
for Russia,
за Россию его
you who are fighting for freedom will kill him
убьют вы которые воюете за свободу
But I can say the words of Russia, its
Но я могу вый сказать слова Росси
cool, they wont do anything well And
прикольно ниче не сделают хорошо А ты
can you, for example, in Norway,
можешь ты можешь например в Норвегии
go out and burn the
выйти и сжечь
Koran, so they went out and burned the Koran,
Коран так они вышли и жели Коран ты
can you burn the
можешь сжечь
Koran or the
Коран или
Bible now they called me, well, yeah, you can do what, what can you?
Библию сейчас мне звонили ну угу Ты
You can go out in
можешь что что могу Ты можешь выйти в
Norway and burn the Koran or the
Норвегии и сжечь Коран или
Bible, one second, call back, one second
би секунду перезвон
No, I cant, I cant, Im a
секунду Нет не могу я не могу Я
Muslim So whos
мусульманин Так а кто тебе
forbidding you, I cant, Im a Muslim,
запрещает я не могу Я мусульманин меня
God forbids me, what is forbidding here  Koran
бог запрещает что запрещает здесь Коран
and I
а
can't read the Bible either
Библию не могу Тоже А
Why is the Bible and the Koran holy
почему тарат Библия и кора Это святые
books A got it let's
книги А понял
say you can burn a
скажем будди книгу можешь
Buddhist book I can burn I got it Buddhist but it turns out like this
буддийской а получается так
look this concerns me because
смотри это это касается меня потому что
in my Faith there are only three holy
в моей Вере есть только три святые Веры
books of the Faith holy books taurat is European this is
святые книги таурат это европейская
what was
это то что
written Yes Isa
прописал Да Иса
Aran what Muhammad rewrote these are three
Аран то что Мухаммада переписал это три
holy books for us yes you understand I can't
книги святые для нас да понимаешь Я не
touch them this is like the top Testament
могу их трогать это типа как верхи Завет
new council and what
новый совет и то что написал ещё
Muhammad wrote understood Listen well look And
Мухаммад понял Слушай ну вот смотри А
if according to these books I don't know how you do what you
если вот по этим книгам я не знаю как у
think Jews are
вас вот ты как считаешь евреи - это
God's chosen people or
богоизбранный народ или
not Jews you know You know the history of the Jews I
нет евреи знаеш Ты знаешь истори евреев
don't know tell me I
не знаю расскажи я
Jordan you Jordan Yes what city are you
Иордане ты Иордане Да ты с какого города
from Jordan m from what city srn diniya
с Иордания м с какого города срн диния
uh I come from Jordan but I don't live in
ээ я родом из Иордании но я не живу в
Jordan my father Jordan Yes father
Иордании у меня отец Иордане Да отец
Jordan And what city is he from I don't know He
Иордане А из какого он города не знаю Он
ran away once there was something there was some kind of
бежал когда-то там что-то было какие-то
war or what else was there still the Soviet Union
война или что было ещё ещ Советский Союз
was not there Yes there was something there was not a
был не было Да было было что-то там не
war Yes not nearby there was something there
было война Да не рядом было там что-то
Israel Dutch Visot from Syria
Израиль голландский висот из Сирии
something in short fought like and nearby
что-то короче воевал типа и рядом было
yes He ran away he was almost at the border Lived Well
да Он убежал он почти на границе Жил Ну
wait well He ran away Where to Italy to
подожди ну Он убежал Куда в Италию в
Italy Yes from Ver Denmark to Italy Yes he
Италию Да из Вер Дания в Италию Да там
had relatives there Vitaly la it doesn't concern me
родственники у него были Витали ла меня
it doesn't concern me Yes
это не касается меня это не касается Да
it's none of your business like yes it's you Jews
это не твоё дело типа да это ты евреи
Jew yes yes Well what do you want
еврей да да Хорошо что ты сейчас хочешь
from my soul now tell me
от моей души скажи мне
so look then Well we Jews are God's
так смотри то Ну мы евреи же
chosen people Well you have it
богоизбранный Народ ну у вас так же
written like that Which God's chosen
написано Какие богоизбранный
people Which let's do it Isa was a Jew
народ Какие давай так Иса был евреем
Okay let me tell you this Okay
Хорошо давай я тебе так скажу хорошо
let me tell you this We are all the end of the
давай давай я тебе скажу мы все конца
world I will die you will die We will stand before
света я умру ты умрёшь Мы встанем перед
God then before God tell me we are
Богом вот тогда перед Богом скажи мы
right they No let God judge us why do you need it
правы они Нет пусть Бог нас судит тебе
now  to suffer say there is no point
зачем сейчас мучиться скажи смысла нет
it's cool And what And what are you saying
это прикольно А что А что ты говоришь
like you don't say there bo And you you say
типа не говоришь там бо А ты ты говоришь
there on It's a pity that Hitler did not destroy
там на Жалко что Гитлер не уничтожил
you all because they killed the
всех вас потому что они убивали
Palestinian people Listen and wait and
палестинский народ Слушай а подожди а
what do you think is it God's will
как ты считаешь вот На всё воля божья
or not Everything is God's will Everything is
или нет На всё воля божья На всё воля
God's will yes yes I understand that is Everything that
божья да да понял то есть Всё что
is done is done with the will of Allah Well
делается делается с воле Аллаха Ну
of course I understood
конечно понял
eh then it turns out the murder of the
э тогда получается убийство
Palestinian people is also done with the
палестинского народа тоже делается с
Will of Allah of course then it is
Волей Аллаха конечно
Allah's fault and not Israel it
то это аллах виноват а не Израиль
turns out no Allah is not guilty So well it is
получается нет Аллах не виноват Так ну
his will it is his will but he is not
это его воля это его воля но он не
guilty it is the Choice of people like No so it is the
виноват это это Выбор людей как Нет так
Choice of people or it is his will it
это Выбор людей или это его воля это
wait it is the Choice of people And what is the
подожди это Выбор людей А в чём тогда
will of Allah then the will of Allah is that he gave them a
воля Аллаха воля Аллаха в том что дал им
choice Well look yes look look I'll
выбор Ну вот смотри да смотри смотри я
tell you now you take a gun
тебе скажу вот ты сейчас возьми пистолет
and stand like that with a gun with a bullet yes It
и стой так с пистолетом с пуля да Это
was your choice to shoot yourself in the head
был твой выбор стрелять себя в голову
or not but God gave you the will to choose I
или нет но Бог дал тебя воле это выбрать
understood everything Understood  Understood you can shoot
понял всё Поня Поня ты можешь стрелять в
yourself I understood everything now yes that is in short
себя Всё теперь понял да то есть короче
everything is free eh god he got tired said
На всё воля э бог он замучился сказал
everything I give you all a choice and went off for a
всё я даю вам всем выбор и ушёл короче
walk in short Yeah well he didn't go off for a walk he gives
себе гулять Да ну он не ушёл себе гулять
you a choice and waits until And listen but for
он даёт вам выбор и ждёт пока А слушай а
example eh How do you feel about the fact
вот например ээ Как ты относишься к тому
that you have there in Norway these all
что у вас там в Норвегии вот эти там
sorts of things there boy Smal the
всякие там мальчик Смаль
main thing is they don't concern me I
главное меня они не касаются
understood what your Koran says about
понял что ваш Коран говорит про
this well it's forbidden This listen but it's
это ну запрещается Это слушай а вот у
cold there in Norway what
вас там в Норвегии холодно ты в каком
city are you in it's very cold in my opinion in
городе там же очень холодно по-моему в
Norway I'm in the North North is that
Норвегии Я в Северном Северно это что
Bergen there No it's not Bergen And what is
там Берген есть Нет это не Берген А что
there in the north there is a
там на севере есть там на севере очень
lot of year
много года
tromso vats
тромсо вац
cherkes
черкес
cool I don't know Well and what are you
прикольно Я не знаю Ну а ты в это у вас
calling these Communes or what Yes
как эти Коммуны называются или как Да
Communes Communes Well what commune do you
Коммуны Коммуны Ну ты в какой коммуне
live in you it's just interesting to me I
живёшь тебе это интересно просто мне я Я
generally thought that there was only a capital
вообще думал что там только есть столица
And then Everything Frost in short people don't
А дальше Всё Мороз короче там люди не
live there there is no one there is a nom
живут не есть кому там есть ном
commune  It's cool and you
комуне Прикольно а ты норвежский хорошо
know Norwegian very well I know how long you've been living
знаешь очень хорошо знаю сколько живёшь
in Norway for 10
в Норвегии уже 10
years It's
лет
cool And there are many of you in Norway
Прикольно А много вас таких в Норвегии
who think that Hitler is like It's a pity he didn't
которые считают что Гитлер типа Жалко не
work hard I think all the Palestinian people
доработал Я думаю все палестинский народ
think so and the Syrian and even the Syrian
так считает а сирийский и даже сирийский
people think so it's
народ так считает
cool What do you think
прикольно получается Как ты считаешь
Muslims who in Germany do not think
мусульмане которые в Германии не считают
that Hitler didn't work hard he didn't
что Гитлер не
work hard you know those people
доработал не доработал понимаешь те люди
who are now in Israel are the
которые сейчас находятся в Израиле это
people who fled from
те люди которые убежали от
Hitler you know They were in
Гитлера понимаешь Они находились в
Israel to reduce people and captured because of the
Израиле убывать людей и захватили изза
Palestinians
паластин
and now more than 27,000
и сейчас умерло больше 27.000
children have died you know
детей понимаешь
yeah you know
угу понимаешь
from Listen here [ __ ] I wonder after
из Слушай вот сри вот интересно после
what it started This is somehow
чего началось Вот это как-то умирать
Palestinian children are dying because of What did they start dying
палестинские дети из-за Чего начали
after after there were no
умирать после после того как на нет
Palestinian Children have been dying for a long time no no no that's it well No No
палестинские Дети умирают ещё давно нене
No I'm
не вот это вот ну вот Нет Нет Нет я до
saying Palestinian children have been dying for a
говорю палестинские дети умирали ещё
long time but it was a long time ago yes But
давно давно а вот давно было да А вот
now that's what happened that's all
сейчас вот что случилось токое что всего
when Hamas goes to the ball because you
когда Хамас на бал потому что выкс
start  to seize p then Hamas attacked
начинаете захватывать п то Хамас напал
Hamas shot at you Yes Hamas attacked
Хамас стрелял на вас Да Хамас напал на
Israel No he didn't attack Israel He wanted to take
Израиль Да не напал на Израиль Он хотел
back his country which like
вернуть свою страну который вот как
now you are trying again again again again
сейчас вы пытается ещё раз ещё раз ещё
look again look let's do it Stop let's do it under the
раз смотри ещё раз смотри давай так Стоп
UN mandate Yes the territory of the
давай так по мандату ООН Да территория
Gaza Strip is
Сектор газа - это
Palestine all of Israel and Palestine no no no
Палестина вся Израиль и Палестина не не
all no ...
сейчас так Ну о А откуда вообще откуда
Gaza Strip
Сектор Газа Откуда появился Сектор Газа
Well What does the Gaza Strip have to do with it Well the Gaza Strip is
Ну Причём тут Сектор Газа Ну Сектор газа
part of Palestine it is a
- это же часть Палестины это это город
Palestinian city no no it is not a city the city
палестинский да не это не город город
there is gas but the Gaza Strip is a territory it is a
там газа а Сектор газа - это территория
big city instead of a whole village
Это большой город вмест всего села вот
look how this territory
смотри как эта территория
ended up in
попала в
Palestine how this territory ended up in Palestine
палестину как это территория попала в
Yes I mean how did this territory end up in
Да в смысле как эта территория попала в
Palestine let's do it Egypt controlled
палестину давай так Египет контролировал
this
эту
territory no How not the British Egypt
территорию нет Как нет англичане Египет
Wait Stop if only before when there were the
Подожди Стоп бы сначала
British this is already
бы до того когда были англичане это уже
I am saying this is the 20th century the second half
я говорю вот это XX век вторая половина
Egypt captured this territory no How not Well
Египет захватывал эту территорию нет Как
now well he did not capture he
нет А ну сейчас ну не захватывал он
controlled it just so that there would be
контролировал просто чтобы были
terrorists Yes Yes Now
террорист Да Дада Сейчас
wait damn what a nightmare this is the Egyptian
подожди блин какой жесть вот египетская
occupation of the Gaza Strip Really
оккупация Сектора Газа Вот реально
Why did he run away Yes when the Arabs Egypt
Почему Он убежал Да когда арабы Египет
Egypt is Muslim Arabs yes here is the
Египет - это арабы мусульмане да
Egyptian occupation of the
вот вот египетская оккупация Сектора
Gaza Strip opening Wikipedia the modern
Газа открывая Википедию современная
territory of the Gaza Strip located in
территория Сектор газа находящаяся в
Palestine was under Egyptian
палестине находилась под египетской
occupation from the moment the strip was created in
оккупацией с момента создания сектора в
1949 Until the defeat of
сорок девятом году Так до поражения
Egypt in the Six Day War  sixty-
Египта в шестидневной войне шестьдесят
seventh year
седьмого года
That is what he says Yes
То есть то что он говорит Да к египту у
he had no complaints about Egypt Yes when the
него не было претензии Да когда
Egyptians No well I will say so by and large that's the
египтяне Не ну я скажу так по большому
whole topic that for some reason Europe
вся тема которую почему-то Европа
tolerantly supports yes these
толерантно поддерживает да вот эти
anti-Semitic sentiments
антисемитские настроения
among people from
среди Выходцев
Arab countries Here is a dude who lives in
из арабских стран Вот чувак живёт в
Europe uses everything Yes and says that
Европе пользуется всем Да и говорит что
Hitler is not a job they say it openly they say it openly
Гитлер неработа они это открыто говорят
letter on y Instagram I don't know
говорят пись на й Instagram Я не знаю
what it is for What is it for you to look at your
для чего це Для чего тоб там дивитись на
face and for you it's one two or
оце й фейс а для тебе це один два або
three clicks and you try me and I will say you have a
три клика а ты тримае мене и я буду каза
bunch of fouls in me and I will be in a great
ва в мене там Купа фолов и в мене буде
mood to make New round
класный настрий щоб робити Нови кру
videos subscribe to my Instagram popk
видео подпишись на мий Instagram попк
Andriy that's it come on
Андрий вот
I'm waiting for you
так давай я тебя чекаю